Now that we have all of our calendar information here,
我们已经在这里显示了所有日历信息
the next thing we need to do is actually render our calendar.
下一步是渲染日历
So what we can do is, in your terminal,
转到终端
go ahead and run yard add and the name of this component is udacifitness-calendar.
运行 yard add 该组件的名称是 udacifitness-calendar
Once that is installed go ahead and restart
安装完毕后 重启应用
your app and head back over to your History.js file.
回到 History.js 文件
So what we will need is obviously we'll need to import this.
我们需要导入 UdaciFitnessCalendar
So we'll say UdaciFitnessCalendar which is coming from what we just barely installed.
来自于我们刚刚安装的组件
So now what we need to do is instead of
现在我们不再渲染
rendering just a stringified version of this.props,
this.props 的字符串化版本
what we want to do instead is
而是渲染日历
render our calendar and there's some things we need to pass it.
并且需要传入一些内容
So first let's go ahead and grab entries,
首先获取 entries
which is basically our whole calendar coming off of this.props.
也就是 this.props 提供的完整日历
So UdaciFitnessCalendar takes a few different things,
向 UdaciFitnessCalendar 传入几项参数
takes some items which is just our entries.
首先是一些 items 即 entries
It's going to take a renderItem property as well as a renderEmptyDate property.
然后是 renderItem 属性和 renderEmptyDate 属性
So this one what it's going to do,
对于这个属性
is we're going to pass it a function which is going to return some ui or
我们向其传入一个函数
return some JSX that will be rendered
并返回一些 UI 或一些 JSX
whenever the calendar is going to render a specific day,
当日历渲染特定的某一天时 将渲染它
and if that day is empty then
如果这一天为空
whatever JSX is returned from
则渲染传递给 renderEmptyDate 的
this function we passed to renderEmptyDate is going to be rendered.
这个函数返回的 JSX
So let's go ahead and look at what that looks like.
我们看看是什么情况
So for a renderItem we'll just create a method
对于 renderItem
called the renderItem and for renderEmptyDate,
我们将创建一个方法 叫做 renderItem
we will create, as you can probably guess,
对于 renderEmptyDate 你可能已经猜到了
a method call renderEmptyDate.
我们将创建一个方法 叫做 renderEmptyDate
So first let's say renderItem and what this is going to do,
首先输入 renderItem
is it's going to pass an object which has a today property as well as all of our metrics.
它将传入一个对象 其中具有 today 属性以及所有的指标
So what this item is going to be is it's either going to be,
这个项目将成为...
let's say something, let's to go to add entry.
我们转到 AddEntry 文件
It's going to look like this or it's going to look,
它将看起来是这样的
let's go to our helpers,
我们转到 helpers 文件
or it's going to look like this depending
或者看起来是这样的
on whatever's in our redux state for that specific day.
具体取决于当天的 redux 状态
So really this is just going to be the day coming from our redux store.
因此这个将是 redux store 中的日期
The next item, we're going to get a formattedDate and then we will get a key.
下一项是 formattedDate 然后获得 key
So what we want to do here,
我们将在这里…
let's change these into parentheses so we get that implicit return.
将这个改成小括号 以便获得隐式返回内容
So we will say view, and then we will say if today is a thing,
输入 View 如果 today 存在的话
so we haven't entered our information for today,
表示我们没有输入当天的信息
we'll just use JSON.stringify again,
再次使用 JSON.stringify
passing in today and if today is not
传入 today
a thing then that means this is a previous day where we have entered in information.
如果 today 不存在的话 意味着这是我们已经输入信息的上一天
So we will just pass in metrics.
我们直接传入 metrics
So that's all renderItem is going to do for right now.
renderItem 暂时就是这些作用
Next, we will have renderEmptyDate which is going to be
接着 输入 renderEmptyDate
called if the specific item in our redux date for that day is null.
如果在 redux 状态中这一天的特定项为空 则 renderEmptyDate 被调用
So what we'll do this is also going to be passed a formattedDate,
同样传入 formattedDate
and we don't need to make this an arrow function because we're not using this queue,
这个不需要成为箭头函数 因为我们在括号里使用这个关键字
we're inside of it, so we can take that off.
因此可以删了这些
And what we're going to do here is let's just return a view
在这里返回一个 View
which has a view as I just mentioned.
里面具有文本
And we will just say no data for this day.
内容为 No Data for this day
All right. So this looks pretty good now.
现在看起来挺正常
So when the calendar renders,
当日历被渲染时
if we've entered in information for this specific day,
如果我们输入这一天的信息
we'll get this ui right here and if we haven't,
我们将获得这个 UI
then we will get this ui.
如果没有输入 则获得这个 UI
And what we can actually do is because we are just rendering this component,
因为我们只是渲染这个组件
there's no need to have this view component right here.
因此没必要在这里添加这个 view 组件
So let's fix this indentation real quick
快速调整下缩进格式
and then now what I want to do is app.js right here.
现在转到 App.js 文件
I'm just going to add a view.
添加一个 View
We'll say height of 20 just to get that status bar out of the way for now,
将 height 设为 20 暂时将状态栏挪开
eventually we'll replace this with an actual status bar,
最终会将这个替换为实际的状态栏
but for now this view will work.
暂时视图能正常显示
So now if we refresh this,
现在刷新下应用
what we should see is now we have our calendar here.
这里出现了日历
And if we select a day,
如果选择一天
you'll notice that we get all of the days starting at the day we
屏幕上将显示所选日期
selected on as well as the information for that day,
以及之后日期的所有信息
or if there is no information for that day,
如果当天没有信息
then we get no data for this day.
则提示：No Data for this day